adworkmedia.com 2014-05-23

# Privacy Policy | AdWork Media

This Privacy Policy applies to AdWorkMedia.com's collection, use, storage and disclosure of information by AdWork Media on its (a) websites, including all its divisions, subsidiaries and related companies (collectively, the Website), (b) on various third party websites, and (c) to AdWork Media's other information collection, including the purchase of customer lists from third parties. 

**Data Integrity**  
AdWork Media takes your privacy seriously. All sensitive information is encrypted with SSL and our server is routinely audited to ensure a secure environment for AdWork Media users. 

**Cookies**  
AdWork Media uses cookies to identify the individual with his or her corresponding tracking data that resides in AdWork Media's database. Individuals who use the Website need to accept cookies in order to use all of the features and functionality of the Website.

**Web Beacons**  
A web beacon is a small pixel image that is placed on a website or in an email which is used to monitor behavior of a user visiting a website or email and store their information. This allows AdWork Media to track certain web sites an individual visits online. Web beacons are used to determine products or services an individual may be interested in, and to track online behavioral habits for marketing purposes.

**Tracking Data**  
To ensure fraud-free service, AdWork Media's lead tracking system gathers IP addresses and other user variables along with setting tracking cookies. This information is used to prevent users from abusing advertiser terms and conditions with methods such as multiple completions per person and fraudulent completions. 

**Outside Information**  
AdWork Media may receive information about individuals from Third Parties or from other sources of information outside of AdWork Media including information located in public databases (Outside Information).

**Individual Information**  
As used herein, Individual Information means Survey Information, Third Party List Information, Other Information, Technology Information, and Outside Information, and any other information AdWork Media gathers or receives about individuals such as usage data, file transfer and viewing data.  
**  
Children's Online Privacy Protection Act**  
AdWork Media will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 13. If AdWork Media obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personal information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from our database. Because it does not collect such information, AdWork Media has no such information to use or to disclose to Third Parties. AdWork Media has designed this policy in order to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA).

**California Residents**  
As per California Civil Code Section 1798.83, California residents may request information about the disclosure of their personal details to third parties by contacting us. 

**Deleting & Updating Your Information**  
If you would like to delete or update the personally identifiable information that we have collected from you (name, address, etc.), simply send your request to [Support@AdWorkMedia.com](mailto:Su%70por%74%40AdWo%72%6BM%65dia%2Ecom). We will process your request, where possible and subject to the terms and conditions contained herein, within a reasonable period of time after receipt. To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**Legal Process**  
AdWork Media may disclose Individual Information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, and other legal processes.  
**  
Advertiser Cookies and Web Beacons**  
AdWork Media does not control Advertisers' use of tracking mechanisms and AdWork Media has no responsibility for the use of such technology to gather information about individuals.

**Links**  
The Website and email messages sometimes contain hypertext links to the web sites of Third Parties. AdWork Media is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other web sites. Linked web sites may contain links to web sites maintained by Third Parties. Such links are provided for your convenience and reference only. AdWork Media does not operate or control in any respect any information, software, products or services available on such Third Party web sites. The inclusion of a link to a web site does not imply any endorsement of the services or the site, its contents, or its sponsoring organization.

**International**  
Anyone using the Website outside of the United States acknowledges that personal information will be collected and stored by AdWork Media in the United States. By using the Website, you consent to the transfer of information to and/or storage of information outside of your country and in the United States. 

**Information collected from Third Parties**  
AdWork Media collects information from individuals when an individual provides information to a Third Party and AdWork Media subsequently purchases, licenses, or otherwise acquires the information from the Third Party (the Seller). Such purchased information may include, but is not limited to, an individual's name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), SMS messaging details (e.g. date, time and content of the SMS message), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, industry of employment, personal and online interests, and such other information as the individual may have provided to the Seller (together, Third Party List Information). When acquiring Third Party List Information, AdWork Media seeks assurances from the Seller that the Seller has a right to transfer the Third Party List Information to AdWork Media and that the Seller has a right to provide offers from advertisers to the individuals whose personal information is included on the Seller's list.

**Contact**  
If you have any questions or comments related to this privacy policy please [contact us](https://www.adworkmedia.com/contact-us.php).
